Finding Aid for the Roderic Gorney papers, 1974-1980
UCLA Library Special Collections
Roderic Gorney papers
1974-1980
285
Roderic Gorney (1924- )
36 boxes (36 linear ft.)
Roderic Gorney (1924- ) is a clinical professor of psychiatry at UCLA's Semel Institute for Neuroscience and Human Behavior. He is a practicing psychiatrist-psychoanalyst, a published author, and has focused his clinical teaching on psychotherapy and pharmacotherapy of adults. His book, The Human Agenda (1972), was nominated for the 1972 Pulitzer Prize. The research contained in this collection was conducted in the mid-1970s and concentrates on the impact of television adults. It contains grant proposal, and research documentation.
University of California, Los Angeles. Library Special Collections. Los Angeles, California 90095-1575
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF. Advance notice is required for access to the collection. Please contact UCLA Library Special Collections for paging information.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Roderic Gorney, 1994.
Biography
Roderic Gorney (1924- ) is a clinical professor of psychiatry at UCLA's Semel Institute for Neuroscience and Human Behavior. He received is Bachelor's and Medical Degrees from Stanford University, and earned a PhD from the Southern California Psychoanalytic Institute. Gorney entered private practice in San Francisco until 1962 when he was invited to join the faculty at UCLA's School of Medicine. He is a practicing psychiatrist-psychoanalyst, a published author, and has focused his clinical teaching on psychotherapy and pharmacotherapy of adults. Gorney is also the founder/director of The Ashley Montagu Institute (1997), a tax-exempt public charity whose mission is to disseminate, extend, and implement the life work of anthropologist Ashley Montagu. He is a member of various associations: American Medical Association, California Medical Association, American Psychiatric Association, American Association for the Advancement of Science, and others.
Gorney is the author of professional articles ranging in subject from the effects of the menstrual cycle to the psychodynamics of SCUBA diving. A generalist whose concern has been to integrate findings of disparate fields in the service of human survival, Dr. Gorney lectured and published widely. His paper, "Interpersonal Intensity" won the 1971 prize of the American Psychiatric Association for essays on alternatives to violence. His book, The Human Agenda (1972), was nominated for the 1972 Pulitzer Prize; was recommended for the 1972 National Book Award, and was nominated for the 1972 Hofheimer Prize of the American Psychiatric Association for outstanding research in psychiatry and mental hygiene. In addition, Gorney served as a consultant for various organizations including the President's Committee on Mental Retardation (1975), Royal Commission of Inquiry on Violence in the Communication Industry (Ontario, Canada, 1976), American Psychiatric Association Task Force on the Effects of Television on Mental Health (1976), National Citizens Committee for Broadcasting (1977), and for California's Attorney General (1977). Because of his research, Gorney was asked to testify for the National PTA in the 1970s on effects of TV violence on children and provided briefings for the same to the House Subcommittee on Communications in Washington DC.
Gorney's research contained in this collection was conducted under the auspices of the Department of Psychiatry's Program on Psychosocial Adaptation and the Future, which he founded and directed in 1971, and concentrated on the impact of dramatic entertainment on adults and the cultural determinants of achievement, aggression, and psychological distress. Roderic Gorney believed human behavior could be transformed positively through mass communication, and human survival might be dependent upon it. From his findings of the study contained here, and with co-research Gary Steele, Gorney published "Human Survival and Mass Entertainment," which was also presented at a Special Conference on World Futures Research in Rome, 1974.
Scope and Content
The bulk of the collection pertains to a large study done in the mid-1970s measuring television effects on attitudes and values in adults. Grant proposals and applications to the NIH, NIMH, NSF, Rockefeller and the Lilly Foundation are included, as well as participant files, program materials, computer data, and reference materials. Also in the collection are U-matic video tape recordings of cable television shows viewed by participants before and after filling out questionnaires and surveys. Boxes containing participant files are have restricted access.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Grants and Proposals
Research Study Documentation
Reference Materials
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
Gorney, Roderic, 1924- --Archives.; University of California, Los Angeles. Dept. of Psychiatry and Biobehavioral Sciences --Faculty --Archival resources.; Psychiatrists --California --Los Angeles --Archival resources.
Items Removed from the Collection
Items removed from the collection include work-study personnel files, empty folders, computer printouts regarding computer center print charges, photocopies of checks issued on PSAF funds, key punch card decks labeled "duplicate."
Container List
- 1. Personnel Files
  - Gorney, Roderic, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes CV and headshots.
  - Long, John M., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes CV.
  - Loye, David (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Loye, David (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Steele, Gary, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 2. Grants, Proposals, and Funding
  - General Support Research Grant: NPI, November 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reports and requests to NPI for budget support, Spring 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - NSF/RANN Proposal: Guidelines, correspondence w/ NSF, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NSF/RANN Proposal: Original, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - NSF/RANN Proposal: "Test Battery and Handbook for Measurement of Television Effects", April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Occidental College, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - MS Copies, Test Battery and Handbook Appendices, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - NIMH Site Visit, preparation materials, August 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - NIMH correspondence regarding grant application, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NIMH Grant proposal, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Proposal materials, appendices C-G, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Mass entertainment, Cultural Patterns, and Human Survival," Appendix to Proposal (A-H), undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - NIMH notes for consideration, March 31, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Generalized Funding Proposal, based on NSF/RANN (draft), April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Generalized Funding Proposal, based on NSF/RANN, Original, May 1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - NIMH Proposal and Appendices, Research Coordinator's Copy, May 1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - PSAF Research Proposal, "Test Battery and Handbook for Measurement of Television Effects" (Office copy), May 1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dissemination plans, prospectus (Lilly), February 1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Lilly Dissemination Grant Report, April 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Proposal materials, appendices drafts, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Lilly Endowment correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Lilly Foundation correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Lilly Financial forms, PSAF, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Human subject protection committee - UCLA, November 1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Human subject protection committee -- NSF/RANN proposal, April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Human subject protection committee -- NSF/RANN proposal, materials related to submission, April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Human subject protection committee -- NIMH original of submission, May 1975 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - PSAF Research Proposal (NIMH), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Research Proposal (draft): MEHS Revised, Pro-social TV Study, April 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - PSAF: UCLA UD Account, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Support Research Grant: NPI, August 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - David Loye files -- NSF Research proposal -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Mass Entertainment, Cultural Patterns and Human Survival -- Restricted, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Human subject protection committee -- NIMH materials related to submission, May 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Human subject protection committee -- Lily/Theta original of submission, August 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Human subject protection committee -- Lily/Theta materials related to submission, August 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Network correspondence regarding TV study (ABC, CBS, NBC), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 3. Research Study
  - PSAF Questionnaires and inkblot responses, wives and husbands #s 01147 - 01216 -- Restricted, September and October 1974 (Box 10)
    Missing 01168 to 01199.
  - PSAF Questionnaires and inkblot responses, wives and husbands #s 01217 - 01241 -- Restricted, September and October 1974 (Box 11)
  - PSAF Questionnaires and inkblot responses, wives and husbands #s 01242 - 01314 -- Restricted, September and October 1974 (Box 12)
  - PSAF Questionnaires and inkblot responses, wives and husbands #s 01315 - 01418 -- Restricted, September and October 1974 (Box 13)
  - PSAF Questionnaires and inkblot responses, wives and husbands #s 01419 - 01441 -- Restricted, September and October 1974 (Box 14)
  - PSAF Questionnaires and inkblot responses, wives and husbands #s 01442 - 01518 -- Restricted, September and October 1974 (Box 15)
  - PSAF Questionnaires and inkblot responses, wives and husbands #s 01519 - 01573 -- Restricted, September and October 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1-61)
    Missing 01526-01560.
  - Follow up questionnaires, Group A (Husbands and Wives evaluation of study) -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Follow up questionnaires, Group B (Husbands and Wives evaluation of study) -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Follow up questionnaires, Group C (Husbands and Wives evaluation of study) -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Follow up questionnaires, Group D (Husbands and Wives evaluation of study) -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Follow up questionnaires, Group E (Husbands and Wives evaluation of study) -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Husbands #100s (1 of 2) -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Husbands #100s (2 of 2) -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Husbands #200s -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Husbands #300s -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Husbands #400s -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Husbands #500s -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Wives #100s (1 of 2) -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Wives #100s (2 of 2) -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Wives #200s -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Ideation, drafts: figures -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Ideation, drafts: manuscript -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Behavior, drafts: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Personality, drafts: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Fantasy, drafts: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Fantasy, drafts: figures -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Fantasy, drafts: manuscript -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Fantasy, drafts: manuscript materials -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Attitudes, drafts: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Values, drafts: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Wives #300s -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Cross-modal, drafts: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Demographic, drafts: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Finished art -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Mood, finished art: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Mood, finished art: figures -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Ideation, finished art: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Behavior, finished art: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Attitudes, finished art: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Values, finished art: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Cross-modal, finished art: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Wives #400s -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Demographic, finished art: tables -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Returned participant comments and notes -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Film codes and scores list -- Restricted, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Questionnaire tags for DEL follow up study -- Restricted, February 1976 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence -- Comstock, George (RAND) -- Restricted, June to October 1975 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence -- K. Lawrence Landers memos -- Restricted, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence -- Ard, Ben N. -- Restricted, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence -- Barron, Frank -- Restricted, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence -- Carpenter, Garrett -- Restricted, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence -- Carter, Rosalynn -- Restricted, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Follow up questionnaires regarding political and social views, Wives #500s -- Restricted, June 1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Leer, Norman -- Restricted, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence -- Masserman, Jules -- Restricted, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence -- Menninger, Roy -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence -- National Association for Better Broadcasting (NARB) Frank Orme -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence -- Rokeach, Milton -- Restricted, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence -- Roman, Melvin -- Restricted, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence -- Singer, Leo -- Restricted, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence -- TV Miscellaneous -- Restricted, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence -- Correspondence with TV network people -- Restricted, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence -- Larry Landers memos -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Results / data analysis of follow up questionnaires -- Restricted, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- Slaby, Ronald B. -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence -- October Mailing: Letters, Etc. -- Restricted, undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence -- Writer's Guild of America: information, correspondence -- Restricted, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence -- Unsorted -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence -- PSAF -- Restricted, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence -- Miscellaneous PSAF -- Restricted, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence -- Grants, general information -- Restricted, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Final report, tables and drafts for mood and ideation -- Restricted, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mood, drafts and manuscript -- Restricted, July 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Mood, first draft -- Restricted, August 1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Ideation, drafts: tables -- Restricted, July 19, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Stimuli Selection -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Project notes, follow-up letter drafts -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Landers: current (program notes, letter drafts) -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Program notebook, notes letter drafts and copies -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Reprint requests (IICS: DAA MI) -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - American Program Bureau -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Friends of the PSAF newsletter list -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Research Substudies: American Film -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - October Study: Study packet, drafts -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - "Mass Entertainment early results" n.d. -- Restricted, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Project notes, drafts, code lists -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - PSAF TV Rating Form -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Energy Strategies for Healthcare Institutions -- Restricted, August 1975 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Supplemental reading list -- Restricted, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Loye: WPA Paper - "Effects of Violent vs. Prosocial Television on Adult Emotional Stability" -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous -- Health services information and letters -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - GRSG Policy Statement -- Restricted, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Grant funds procedures -- Restricted, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - NPI Account Correspondence -- Restricted, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous finance documents -- Restricted, 1974, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - David Loye files -- miscellaneous items re: PSAF -- Restricted, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - David Loye files -- Requests for TV APA paper -- Restricted, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Theta Cable 1974 -- Restricted (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - David Loye files -- TV: Sociology, etc. journals -- Restricted, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - David Loye files -- TV: Psychology journals -- Restricted, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - David Loye files -- TV: Communications journals -- Restricted, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - David Loye files -- TV: Psychiatry journals -- Restricted, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - David Loye files -- Re: journals -- Restricted, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - David Loye files -- Delayed report letters -- Restricted, 1975, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - David Loye files -- Correspondence -- Restricted, 1975-1975 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Continuing Conference on Liberal Arts (Lilly) Reston, Virginia, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - News clips about Gorney research -- Restricted (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Program notebook notes -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Richard Trubo Material -- Restricted, November 1976 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Reprint requests -- Restricted, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Reference Materials (1 of 6) -- Restricted, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Includes Senate Report for Television Violence, 1974
  - Reference Materials (2 of 6) -- Restricted, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Reference Materials (3 of 6) -- Restricted, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Reference Materials (4 of 6) -- Restricted, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Reference Materials (5 of 6) -- Restricted, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Wife's Packet -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Husband's Packet -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Program notebook notes, codes and scales -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - October Study, 1st Packet -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - October Study, Letter to Reserves -- Restricted, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Reference Materials (6 of 6), Punch cards, Index cards for films and film stars, 1974 (Box 19)
  - PSAF Television Research Questionnaire and example method of delivery, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Research design and data analysis notes, August 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Data subcontracting document notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Notes on Feshbach Singer: TV and violence, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - +, -, 0, neutral track scheduling and television schedules with notes throughout, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Programming information, Fall 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - PSAF TV Rating Form development and TV program lists, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - S Programs Search, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - PSAF blank rating forms, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Stimulus Search: PSAF forms and program lists, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Program information, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Revisions to network president letter, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Rokeach Value Survey (RVS) Procession Workup, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Gallup Field Study Correspondence, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Forms Used by NBC Research, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Research, television violence, 1968-1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Comstock, George (RAND) articles on television research, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Overview Five Year Review of Research Sponsored by the American Broadcasting Company, September 1970 - August 1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bertram S. Brown, M.D. Testimony before the Committee on Internal Security, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Program information and TV Guide, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - D. Loye memo on Fantasy, October 22, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Abstracts of Articles on TV Effects from Psych, Soc. Abstracts, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Priorities for Studies of TV and Behavior" presentation for 1978 Annual Meeting Theme: Time, Age, and Timelessness (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Item listings for possible subscales for possible use, February 10, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - PSAF Television Study: A Summary of Results and Findings checklist, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Press (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - TV Publication Outline, October 23, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Roster of principal academic and popular periodicals, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Reference articles on television and behavior, 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - NBC Study of Relationship between Exposure to Television Drug Advertising and Use by Teenagers of Proprietary and Illicit Drugs, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The Royal Commission on Violence in the Communications Industry Interim Report (Canada), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Mood - memo regarding final touches, editing, tables and figures, June 7, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Situational - Behavior Transfer, tables, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - PSAF Research Memo - Demographic data (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Frequency Distribution guides, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cross-modal Correlations, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - D Group Edited, final stuff, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Mood Notes, April 1976 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mood Raw Transfer notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Ideation - Raw transfer notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - PSAF Program Materials, program notebook (1 of 2), 1973 - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Discriminant Analysis, statistics manual, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Ideation Notes, April 1976 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Ideation Guide shoot one, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Mood tables, Guide sheets, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Fantasy notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Fantasy: Edited, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Fantasy tables and figures, guidelines, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Fantasy - raw transfer, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Attitude - DL Edited, LL ISSR, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Attitude Tables and Figures, guidelines, April 1976 (Box 2, Folder 59)